prophoto.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy » ProPhoto WordPress theme

Downshift, LLC (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates [https://pro.photo](https://pro.photo/) (the“Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site or from users of our WordPress theme, ProPhoto (the “Theme”).

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### Information Collection And Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name and email address (“Personal Information”).

### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this data for the purposes of providing and improving the Site experience and to enable remarketing lists for search ads. You may [opt out of seeing personalized ads](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922) in your Google Ads Settings or use an [Opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

### Third Party Services Integration

Some third party services (like Instagram) require you to login to your account and authorize our Theme to access your account information.  The Theme does not access or store your login information from these services. The Theme does store unique keys/identifiers provided by the third party service allowing the Theme to retrieve the requested account data. These keys are stored in the database where the theme is hosted, not at our Site.

### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you regarding new product releases, or other information that we determine to be critical or highly valuable to you.

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of **February 19, 2018** and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://pro.photo/contact).
